You're officially under
ship arrest, captain!
Sorry, I...
I moved on.
You did more than that, you idiot!
You could've killed your whole crew!
How can you be so stupid?
Well, we all made it out
all right, didn't we?
That's all that matters.
What was that?
Are you going easy on him, Jinbei?
Is that Conqueror's Haki?
It's not worth it, boss.
Back away, soldier.
You're in the blast zone.
All done?
You patched things up so quickly.
Yep, thanks to the Sunny. She's tough.
Took that fall like a total champ.
Only broke a yard in fact.
Not too shabby.
Captain sure put her
through her paces, though.
Robin, dear!
Your snack is here.
Why, thank you.
Oh.
Her wanted posters.
They're all new.
Wanted posters?
Can I see?
An emperor of the sea and the senior
captain of the Straw Hat fleet.
Straw Hat Luffy and his
nine crewmates are now some
of the most important players
in the world of Pirates.
It's only natural that
their bounties would change.
Did it go up?
The ship's doctor, cotton candy
lover, Chopper, listed as a pet.
Bounty, 1,000 berries.
Up by 900 berries.
Hey!
Is this some kind of joke?
Huh?
Navigator, Cat, Burglar, Nami.
Bounty, 366 million berries.
Why?
Why can't I have that money?
Yo-ho-ho, yo-ho!
Yeah, baby!
Musician Soul King Brooke.
Bounty, 383 million berries. Thank you!
What?
Shipwright, Cyborg Franky.
Bounty, 394 million berries.
Those government bastards!
Where the hell am I?
Sniper, God Usopp.
Bounty, 500 million berries.
Enough!
I don't want it to go up anymore!
This should cheer you up.
Don't be sad.
Archaeologist, demon child, Nico
Robin, bounty, 930 million berries.
Cook, blackleg Sanji, bounty,
1 billion 32 million berries.
Jinbei, here's yours!
Oh, you were kicking ass back there.
You made quite a scene.
Elmsman, first son of the sea, Jinbei.
Bounty, 1,100,000,000 berries.
Swordsman, pirate hunter, Zoro.
Bounty, 1,111,000,000 berries.
Damn it!
I'm lower than him?
But how?
Are you all right, Sanji?
You seem troubled.
I do not need any
sympathy from you, Jinbae.
You're both dead to me. Huh?
Nah, he's fine. Ignore him.
He's just mad because he's number four.
What the hell did you call me?
Just restrict the second,
please. Calm down.
I won't do it again.
Please let me out of here.
Senior captain and an emperor
of the sea, Straw Hat Luffy.
Bounty, three billion berries.
I'm so hungry.
Did you see?
Yeah, that was crazy.
It was really them! No way!
They call the world's
greatest torch, you know?
Outstairs! So cool!
I thought we were finished when the Navy
shut down the warlords
and came for our necks.
But somehow, we're still here.
We've got Buggy to think for that.
Our chairman is the best.
Please spare me!
You can take whatever you want
from here, just let me go!
Hey, thank you.
Come on, I'll do anything you say.
I'll lick your boots, just don't kill me!
You know, when Hawkeye and I found it,
Crossgill, we were hoping
to run it ourselves.
So tell me something, Back.
Why are you the boss?
Well, I mean, all I can
say is I'm real sorry.
I'll have better luck next time.
And that's all it takes to
be an emperor of the sea?
Some crying and a half-hearted apology?
Frankly, it sets a bad
example if we keep you alive.
This is more than just humiliation.
A thousand deaths wouldn't pay
back the insult you've dealt me.
I'd rather you just die.
Well, look who it is!
Hello, boss.
Why, this is just like the
good old days, isn't it?
It would be so nice working for you again.
You worm stabbing me in the back.
Hug Aldino! Am I?
Because I don't recall becoming
your subordinate, buggy.
Two-faced little prick.
Go ahead.
Call me whatever you like.
Well, the chairman is dead. So what now?
You guys got a plan?
I'm happy to serve, crocodile.
Well, this is a dog-eat-dog
world we live in.
Seems you pushed your
luck, buggy boy! Dammit!
I'm gonna bite your finger off!
I hear you've lost your privilege
as a warlord of the sea, Miyok.
And what is your point?
I'd make it quickly.
As you may know, this island is
surrounded by the Navy right now.
They move fast.
Typical of the world
government to put together a
little committee just to pull
the rug out from under you.
I'm sure they were all proud
of themselves at the reverie.
But that's that.
Now you're nothing but
a filthy pirate to them.
They can't wait to cut you down
if it'll make them look better.
You set them on the road to this yourself.
Mind your tongue.
That was a long time ago.
If you're quite finished.
I have a rather urgent move to make.
Good, then why not come here?
You don't have a better plan, do you?
If we team up together, we can form an
organization the Navy will have to respect.
You were known as the Marine
Hunter once upon a time.
Neither of us trust other people.
We have that much in common, at least.
It's not a bad deal, Hawkeye.
What's with that look?
What does he want?
Why do bad things always happen to me?
I've never done a thing wrong!
You gotta come quick!
Stop your crying! Go out and fight!
You're not scared of the Navy, are you?
Buzz off!
I'm trying to sneak away
here and you're ruining it!
Somebody's attacking the Navy ships!
Look, they're all getting sunk!
It's a massacre out there!
But who would help us?
This is scary!
They're so strong!
It's Crocodile!
Get bossed!
Open fire!
I heard rumors that Crocodile
is Captain Buggy's henchmen.
I guess they're true.
His prettiest life on the
line to rescue all of us.
All thanks to Chairman Buggy!
That's right.
Just as I planned. ...pens.
He bored my ass out before and
now he's coming to collect!
I don't have that kind of money!
Why do you think I was borrowing from you?
I'd rather face the Navy!
Surprised you stuck around.
I thought you'd make a run for it.
I was trying to!
Funny thing about business.
It looks like I'm doing well, but
there's just so much overhead,
so many mouths to feed.
Also, my biggest earners were the
giants, and they all walked out.
Oh, so you can't pay.
Slavery it is, then.
We'll sell you off today.
Come on, Krieg baby.
We broke out of Impale Town together.
What about that?
We're impals, right?
Why do you think I lent you
the money in the first place?
But that debt's been paid.
Time for you to hold up your end.
Yeah, but...
I've got a company to fund.
Now, are you gonna pay
what you owe me or not?
Relax, okay?
I've got tons of experience.
I'll help you run your business.
I'm a former warlord of the sea, too.
We'll make a perfect team.
Really?
I'll work off every last berry I owe.
For starters, I'll give your
company one hell of a classy debut.
I've got human resources at the wazoo!
Advertising, printing, transportation!
All at your fingertips!
And the work is free of charge, too!
So, your genius idea for a flyer was this?
I can't help but notice
you're at the top, President.
No, wait a sec.
That was an accident, I promise you!
Well, so is this.
Listen, I swear that wasn't my intention.
This is all my staff's fault.
They worship the ground I walk on, okay?
It took me by surprise, too.
Look at the poster I made.
It's cool.
It's cool, right?
Damn it.
What did you do?
I made you look extra awesome
because you're the best.
You haven't shown this
to anyone yet, right?
Nobody important, boss.
Just everyone in the whole world.
As I'm sure you've heard,
Buggy was the mastermind behind
the Impel Down prison break.
He was even on Roger's crew years ago.
He and Redhead Shanks have quite a
bit of history, so he's no small fry.
Also,
he's so well-liked among
pirates that Crocodile
came to his aid when we
attacked Empty Bluffs Island.
The partnership between Crocodile
and Mihawk was no surprise, though.
We confirmed that through wiretapping.
Shady organizations are already
investing in their marine hunting.
We're seeing a rise in insurgency
all over the world right now.
Cross Guild is feeding into it.
We should consider them
a significant threat.
What are the bounties on
Cross Guild's members?
First up, the former warlord of the sea,
Sir Crocodile His logia-type Devil Fruit
power is still formidable He also has
a strong intellect and leadership skills
His bounty is 1,965,000,000 berries Then,
Hawkeye Mihawk The former
warlord is hailed as
the world's greatest swordsman
Even above red-haired
shanks A man with
extraordinary strength deserves
an extraordinary bounty
3,590,000,000 berries.
Lastly, there's Buggy the Genius Jester.
We spoke about his storied history.
But more than that, he commands
the power of the other two men.
So his bounty is 3,189,000,000 berries.
Just like Straw Hat Luffy, we
consider him to be a new emperor.
In other words, he is a threat
to the world government itself.
Look at you, an emperor—that's
quite the achievement for a clown!
That's enough,
you know;
this might work out in our
favor, don't you think?
He'd be useful as a
figurehead for the guild.
I have no interest in becoming an
emperor; I'd much rather live in peace.
peace and let him carry
that target on his back.
You serious?
We might as well let him
take the heat for a while.
And if we change our
minds, we can kill him.
Fine by me.
Our time is now!
This era!
will require a new vision and new leaders
we founded cross guild
to seize its reigns.
allow me to introduce our
executives first up sir crocodile.
and next the great swordsman hawk guy.
Looks like we're back.
Fools!
You're the best!
We do it right, and do it flashy!
What do you say?
Look!
He's shedding tears of joy!
Oh, Tang it, I'll...
I'm gonna start crashing tears!
I've lost control of my ride!
I see it, Marco. We're here.
Yeah?
All right, I'll be taking off now.
Thanks for the ride. It was fun.
Bye, Shanks.
You're leaving?
You sure you don't want
to join my crew, Marco?
Come on.
Thanks, but no thanks.
You big-shot pirates are too much.
No more babysitting for
me, give me a break!
I'm not that high maintenance.
Tell them back—you want me to lie?
See
ya!
What
you're not gonna come with us—we
were gonna be pirates together!
You felt
what happened back there, didn't you?
When that woodsman attacked, we were on
the verge of defeat. When someone's Haki.
someone's Haki
saved this country.
Kaido is gone, but other
enemies will target us.
And now that I know that...
I'd go crazy if I left!
I can't have a fun adventure while
I'm worried about my friends at home.
You'd feel the same way, right?
But I still want to be
a part of your crew!
Make me an honorary member!
I guess I understand.
That might be good, actually.
If you stay in the land of
Wano, it'll be in good hands.
I'll leave it to you.
Keep Momo safe.
It won't be easy.
Momo has a lot of pride, you know.
He might be stubborn. I am too.
Don't worry about me.
I can handle this.
Yamato, no.
Hey, Straw Hat!
Hey, Marco!
There's a ship nearby that's
going my way, so I'm taking off.
It's been a real adventure.
Sure has.
Have a safe trip! You too.
I wanted to ask.
Back in Marineford.
You saved my life during
that battle, right?
Carry Straw Hat if you won't run! Hurry!
Thanks for that.
Everyone was working hard to save you.
Jinbei 2, why was that?
Oh, well, it's been quite a while.
It's, uh, I recall.
You've come a long way since then.
I'm sure Ace would be real proud of you.
I sure hope so.
Luffy, this age belongs to you now.
Better take good care of it.
Right.
See ya!
Please, sweetie, don't
be so hard on yourself.
He's fine.
It's Sabo.
He'll make it back soon.
Right.
On the bright side, at least
everyone survived the mission.
There you go!
We have to celebrate every little miracle!
Yee-haw!
But golly gee, that darn Sabo!
How dare he make us worry so much!
My little heart can't take all of this!
I wish I knew what happened, but
we were already split up by then.
Still, I believe in Sabo.
Hey, that's my line!
I believed in Sabo way before you did!
In fact, my hopes for him are, Skye...
Would you shut up?
We're an army, not a dance circus.
Dragon.
Sabo will be all right.
However, if he really killed King Cobra,
that's not something I can ever approve of.
It doesn't matter what the reason is.
It's unacceptable.
Now, Kuma, we've done enough speculating.
Why don't you tell me what you saw?
As you wish, master.
As you wish.
We've got an incoming call
to the Kamabaka Queendom.
It could be the Flame Emperor.
Trace it and record the call. Yes, sir.
Badapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadapadu.
Kolic.
Hello?
This is Koala.
It's me.
It's Sabo.
I'm sorry.
I know I've caused you guys trouble.
I'm
It's just a little better.
Just let's dance.
Go up.
Look at him.
Let's sit down.
Let's see what happens.
My patience will change.
There is a lot more power together.
Little love is strong.
I'm so glad we all get this world.